I had never seen…
a drink in my hand freeze
in real time before.
MIDWINTER
It was incredibly cold.
My hands are so cold.
My whole body was cold.
It felt so reckless.
It was impossible. It was just…
SNOWY MOUNTAIN
It was so cold.
I was dazed there.
TARZZAN GROANS
I couldn't even close my hand.
I took off my glove for a moment,
and my hand froze.
SUFFERING
This is so bad.
-Your leg?
-Here. It feels like it's being torn.
I felt so weak.
I was like, "If viewers criticize me
for this, so be it.
It's killing me."
I'd never climbed a mountain before.
I felt I wasn't ready, but I had to go on.
BEGINNER HIKERS'
K-HIKING CHALLENGE
TAKE A HIKE!
Hiking…
Why do you think people go hiking?
Did you find an answer?
DECEMBER, 2025
NEAR NAMSAN, SEOUL
THE DAY OF THE MEMBERS' FIRST MEETING
SININA
THE MEMBERS DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THE PROGRAM YET
Why do I feel so nervous?
SOMEONE ARRIVES EARLY, FEELING NERVOUS
THE FIRST MEMBER ENTERS
Someone's here.
-Hello.
-You scared me.
THIS YOUNG MAN APPEARING
WITH AN INNOCENT SMILE IS…
TARZZAN (REAL NAME: LEE CHAE-WON)
THE OLDEST MEMBER OF ALLDAY PROJECT
AN ALL-ROUND ARTIST WITH A COLORFUL CAREER
BUT THE REAL LEE CHAE-WON
IS AS CUTE AS A MONKEY
What are you holding?
-Our new album's been released.
-Oh, your album?
Thank you.
HE BROUGHT HIS ALBUMS AS GIFTS
FOR THE FIRST MEETING
-Have you been well?
-Have you lost weight?
I have, after the album release.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
-His group's new album.
-Right.
A HEARTFELT HANDWRITTEN LETTER
No, don't read it here.
It's so embarrassing.
HE'S SHYER THAN HE LOOKS
He wrote that he'd do his best.
WHATEVER IT MAY BE, HE'S ENTHUSIASTIC
Did you guess who else would come?
Well, I couldn't even guess.
So when I was told
to open the door earlier,
I thought,
"What if some people are already here?"
"What should I do, then?"
I hadn't been this nervous in a while.
THE MEMBERS DON'T KNOW
WHO THE OTHERS ARE YET
Can I go in and use the bathroom first?
-The bathroom?
-Yes.
THE DOOR OPENS RIGHT AWAY
Filming has already started inside.
Really?
HE GOES IN A HURRY TO ANSWER NATURE'S CALL
They'll be here soon. Wait.
Hello.
CAR, THE GARDEN
-Why are you shy?
-When did you get here?
Why didn't you knock first?
AN UNEXPECTED CHARACTER APPEARS
AT AN UNEXPECTED TIME
Hello.
We met not long ago.
Really?
-Did you meet?
-We met at 10CM's show.
We were too busy with sound check
to go greet you then.
AS SOON AS HE SITS DOWN…
-By the way…
-What?
-Can I go to the bathroom?
-You can't.
-I'm about to go--
-Seriously, no.
It's urgent.
Then I'll just…
OKAY, YOU CAN GO
CAR, THE GARDEN (REAL NAME: CHA JUNG-WON)
BABY AND ME, HUNGRY!
HIGHLY ACTIVE ON YOUTUBE & VARIETY SHOWS
MAIN JOB: SINGER-SONGWRITER
SECOND JOB: ENTERTAINER
A WELL-LOVED, 14-YEAR VETERAN SINGER
HE HAS RETURNED LOOKING REFRESHED
So what's the age gap between you two?
I was born in 2002.
I was born in 1990.
YEAR OF THE HORSE
Twelve years.
I thought
he was younger than that, though.
So you can handle much younger?
What is there to handle?
It's just age.
HE'S JUST A GUY WHO'S 12 YEARS YOUNGER
Then what should I call you?
Mr. The Garden?
Whatever you like.
Garden, the garden, or Jung-won, whatever.
-Call him Car-the.
-Car-the.
That's okay, too.
Car-the, it is.
SILENCE
It'd be nice to learn music from you.
I want to sing better.
Well, I'd like to teach you too,
but something happened recently.
So I'm hesitant to teach.
I'm sure Tarzzan sings better.
I've never sung properly.
Sure, I've sung at karaoke,
but I've never really sung properly.
But I don't think I should teach anyone.
Tarzzan, do you know what happened to him?
No, I don't.
Please. Please, don't watch it.
-Just see me here.
-Hello.
RIGHT THEN, SOMEONE ARRIVES
-What was his name?
-Hello.
-Just see me here.
DOWOON
ANOTHER UNEXPECTED MEMBER
Dowoon of DAY6.
-It's nice to meet you.
-Likewise.
-Nice to meet you.
-Wow.
Do you two know each other?
We just greeted each other once.
-I know Young K.
-That's right.
But Dowoon and I
have never met in private.
What a spectacular lineup.
You think so?
Yes.
I mean, I love being among them!
Gosh, I watched your videos a lot.
I'd only heard your voice before, but…
-Did you watch me?
-Yes.
Really? Wow.
THIS YOUNG MAN IS…
DOWOON, THE DRUMMER OF DAY6
DAY6'S YOUNGEST MEMBER
DOWOON
KNOWN FOR HAVING A LOT OF HOBBIES
Can I ask where you're from?
-You're from Ulsan, right? I'm from Busan.
-Yes.
I have an Ulsan accent.
Mine's a mix of Busan and Changwon.
I also have Busan and Ulsan accents.
-Really?
-Yes.
-So you grew up in Ulsan?
-I did.
So you grew up there and moved to Busan?
I went to high school in Busan.
BECOMING FRIENDS RIGHT AWAY
-An arts high school?
-Yes.
In Geumjeong-gu.
FEELING AWKWARD SINCE HE'S FROM INCHEON
-I went to Busan Arts School.
-We were really close.
Busan Arts School was better.
-On the hill…
-His school was better?
I went to a DAY6 concert,
and what I loved about him is…
You did?
Young K was like,
"We've gone through so much
to come this far."
He was emotional and thanking the fans.
Then he said, "This is nice!"
I was like, "I love him!"
"He's so cool."
IT'S ONE OF HIS CHARMS
It wasn't like that.
I really loved his vibe.
I like you a lot, too.
On YouTube,
I saw your videos,
and the titles were already so funny.
What videos did you watch?
SENSITIVE
What, are you interrogating him?
It's just that recently,
something happened, so…
Because he might've watched that?
The title was…
It was a video someone else filmed.
I love all of your songs
and live performances.
But their videos are like,
"Car, the Garden's
terrible live performance."
They're always titled that way.
-But that was so…
-No, that's not it.
"The live performance of 'Tree'
was a disaster."
Yes, that's it!
But they also upload something
like "It wasn't bad today."
HYPING HIM UP WHILE PUSHING HIM AWAY
He didn't want it brought up.
HYPED UP AND SIDELINED
-But…
-"A disaster."
I think they're a true fan.
There was a dog…
There was a dog emoticon.
Right.
This is the first meeting.
I'm so shy around strangers.
NOW, THE LAST MEMBER ENTERS
It's pure evil.
-Hello.
Hello.
-He's a real actor.
LEE CHAE-MIN
FEELING AWKWARD
-Hello.
-Wow.
-It's unbelievable.
-I felt that way too.
Unbelievable.
Nice to meet you.
ACTOR LEE CHAE-MIN
UP-AND-COMING ACTOR WITH A HANDSOME FACE
AND A WIDE RANGE OF ACTING ABILITIES
AFTER PLAYING LEE HEON
IN BON APPETIT, YOUR MAJESTY,
HE'S BECOME A RISING STAR
WITH A LOT OF UPCOMING PROJECTS
This is actor Lee Chae-min.
Right. Hello.
Hello. It's nice to meet you.
Everyone's so handsome.
THINKING OUT LOUD
Right.
You know his group, right?
ALLDAY PROJECT.
Like this.
AS BEFITS A FORMER MC OF MUSIC BANK
-And him?
-Of course, I know him.
Have you watched his recent video?
You mean, the live performance?
-What was it? Live…
-Everyone watched it.
What was it?
But I liked it.
So did I. The title was so cute.
"A disaster."
So it's even spread
to the acting world like a disease.
That video…
No, I liked your live broadcast too.
SKILL CONTROVERSY BROADCAST
The one where he said how he felt?
I thought it was cool.
In what way?
You know…
GO ON, CHAE-MIN
Well, something like that, I…
You know, I just…
NO REASON
So it was a feeling
that's hard to describe.
-I really love your song "Tree."
-Me too.
Thank you.
All right, so you four are the members.
-It's nice to meet you.
-The pleasure is mine.
We're gathered here today
so we can get to know each other.
-And that's why we did the questionnaire.
-Right.
LIFESTYLE, PHYSICAL ACTIVITY QUESTIONNAIRE
IT WAS SENT TO THEM BEFORE FILMING
ALL FOUR OF THEM COMPLETED IT
All of you will be working together.
I thought it'd be nice for you
to get to know each other better today.
So we'll reveal them to everyone here.
Oh, it was meant to be revealed?
CAR, THE GARDEN
Car, the garden's strengths.
Admits mistakes
and engages in self-reflection fast.
I really do.
It reflects his recent activities.
His weakness is that he's impatient.
-You are?
-I'm so impatient.
I even eat fast.
So I don't like to be part of a group.
Oh, no. He'll scold us a lot.
He'll…
Since I'm so impatient…
So when you drive, do you use high beams?
-I don't.
-No?
I'm not like that.
-Like this.
-No.
I don't even know how to use them.
High beams…
In any case,
I think you're quite impatient.
Your favorite dishes
are mandu and chicken dishes.
You're allergic to cucumbers?
I'm not, but I wrote that
because you might make me eat them.
I thought you wouldn't make me eat them
if I'm allergic.
"What's the most recent book
you've read?" "None."
I read some books of quotations.
Through Reels.
-Reels?
AN UNEXPECTED WAY OF READING
-Reading them through Reels?
-Yes.
Can you tell us some famous sayings?
"Know yourself."
Oh…
You got that from Reels?
EVEN HE FINDS IT RIDICULOUS
-It's a good saying.
-Right.
"If you regularly exercise
for your stamina,
write in detail, such as
which exercise, how many times, etc."
"None."
You must've finished it fast.
It wasn't hard to answer.
"On a scale of 1 to 100, how would you
grade your stamina? And why?"
"Grade: 20 points."
"Reason: I don't exercise
and am gaining weight."
His character is…
"I don't exercise and am gaining weight."
HIS SAD STORY
His character is…
So he does know himself.
I KNOW MYSELF
-Let's see what kind of person Dowoon is.
-Right.
He has a lot of hobbies.
Gaming, fishing,
-plant care.
-Oh, right.
-Tending to plants.
-Plant care?
Boxing, browsing used cars.
Right, that's fun.
I do this lately.
Everyone dreams of certain cars.
Like, "I think I can afford
a car like this." It's so fun.
"Should I buy this or not?"
Right, exactly.
-Imagining.
-Right.
"What is your favorite movie
or drama show?"
The answer is
"The Dream Life of Kim Living in Seoul."
-Seriously. It's a masterpiece.
-Sorry,
but the correct title is
The Dream Life of Mr. Kim.
"The Dream Life of Kim Living in Seoul."
HE DOESN'T KNOW
THE TITLE OF HIS FAVORITE DRAMA
Who is this Kim?
Is he your neighbor?
I wrote it without looking it up.
"The Dream Life of Kim Living in Seoul."
And "Howl's Castle."
Howl's Moving Castle.
It's "Howl's Moving Castle."
NO WONDER IT FELT SHORT
But seriously, I love them.
Yet you wrote the wrong titles.
I think he and I have a lot in common.
Yes, I think so.
We're not so detailed,
but once we start something…
You put it in such a great way.
"Practice kickboxing
three to four times a week."
"Sparring, shadowboxing."
"Kicking."
Who says that?
Who says kicking as a hobby?
Because…
Maybe "practice kicking."
RIGHT, IT'S KICKBOXING
In the beginning, it sounds good.
"Sparring, shadowboxing."
Then, "kicking."
You're right. It sounds awkward.
That was it.
"Which of the following
physical activities do you prefer?"
"Hiking."
Right, I think hiking is really good.
-Have you done it before?
-Sure, I have.
When you reach the top,
you feel so refreshed.
And it feels so cool on the top
in the summer.
"On a scale of 1 to 100,
how would you grade your stamina?"
"Eighty points."
"I haven't exercised in two years,
but my stamina is much better."
What does this mean?
I know what he means.
Do you?
He can translate it.
Translate it for us.
-So, he used to work out regularly.
-Okay.
But he hadn't for two years,
so he thought his stamina would be worse.
But it turns out it's still good.
That's right.
AMAZING TRANSLATION
-Is it accurate?
-Yes, it is.
I used to work out at the gym.
Then I stopped for two years.
THE TWO ARE LIKEMINDED
Next is Chae-min.
LEE CHAE-MIN
"What are your hobbies?"
"Basketball, piano,
learning guitar lately?"
Then are you a member of a club?
Yes.
You're doing it properly.
You also do streetball.
-I love basketball too.
-Really?
I think I've seen you play.
-Maybe not?
On the street?
While passing by?
Honestly, I just said that.
I'm sorry.
At a park in Hangang River?
Yes, and I also play at Banpo Stadium.
Do you live in Banpo?
No, in Cheongdam.
No, no.
Why were you suddenly curious about that?
You see, we shouldn't be like this.
I lied to him just now
without realizing it.
I said I probably saw him.
It was a lie.
We should stop this
to really get close to each other.
"If you have any habit or method
for your stamina…"
"Juice."
-He wrote "Juice."
-Juice?
What kind of juice?
I drink thistle juice,
which is good for the liver.
And cabbage juice,
which is good for the stomach.
I have it every morning.
You parents help you with it?
Like the supplements?
Or by yourself?
-I live alone right now.
-So by yourself?
-So by myself.
-You live alone in Cheongdam?
That's amazing.
No…
You're still on that?
He's intimidated.
I am intimidated.
No, it's not that kind of house.
What you hate the most is hiking.
Why do you hate hiking?
I don't really hate it.
I just haven't done it much,
so I don't know
the beauty of it yet, I think.
So you don't do cardio much?
I don't really like running.
I just like competitive sports.
So I play basketball.
If I have to run, it has to be a race.
Competitive.
Yes, I'm quite competitive.
So you have to crush others.
"Crush others."
You enjoy crushing others.
On a scale of 1 to 100,
you graded your stamina a 70.
-The reason is…
-It's lower than expected.
Right. You work out every day
and play basketball. Why?
Since I work out every day,
I feel tired all the time.
So all the working out
makes your stamina worse?
I think so, but you know, I think…
I enjoy making myself exhausted.
I can't stand just relaxing and resting.
I only relax and rest when I sleep.
You'll definitely make it big…
You're already successful,
but you'll become a superstar.
"Superstar."
-You have the feeling?
-Yes, I do.
In what way?
If I were him, I'd be so completed.
What?
I mean, complacent.
"So complacent."
I heard it wrong.
So that's why everyone was silent.
-All right.
-So lastly,
-the youngest one, then?
-Yes.
TARZZAN
-I'm curious about him the most.
-Me too.
"Usually, I go to bed
around 3 to 4:00 a.m.
and wake up around 1:00 p.m.
SIMILAR HABITS
I knew it. Country folks are alike.
"Country folks."
What does that have to do with this?
My schedule is so tight,
it feels like a day is 48 hours.
So I tend to sleep for a long time.
"What do you think
your strengths and weaknesses are?"
"I'm honest and extreme."
Meaning, "All in or all out."
He's a star.
Those are the traits of a star.
Star? Is that a thing?
TWO RISING STARS
The traits of stars?
His favorite movie shows that too.
A Star is Born.
Me too.
That's my favorite too.
The activity he prefers the most.
He picked swimming.
In the lower grades of elementary school,
I was a triathlete.
Really?
He's the real deal.
SINCE MIDDLE SCHOOL,
HE WON MODERN DANCE COMPETITIONS
The gap between him and the others
are widening.
I like it because…
he can come to the rescue
when I'm in trouble.
-When in trouble?
-Yes.
"On a scale of 1 to 100,
how would you grade your stamina?"
He wrote 60.
You two are fitter than us, though.
"My physical abilities are definitely
not as good as the old days."
On a scale of 1 to 100,
compared to when I used to work out a lot,
my physical abilities are much weaker.
You know yourself best.
Right.
You're so upright, both of you.
"Upright."
All right.
Since it's our first meeting today,
we tried to get to know each other
better through this.
What's most important is actually
what we'll do together.
-I'm so curious.
-So am I.
That's what's important.
All of you have something in common.
We can't lie.
-We're honest.
-Honesty.
Well, what I have in common with them is…
-I'm a man.
-We're men.
And we're Korean.
HE ONLY SPEAKS FACTS
Well, we thought
what you have in common
is that you're about to reach the top.
That you're the next rising stars.
That's what we think.
All four of you here.
You guys are almost there.
You'll soon reach the top.
The four of you can do it.
The four of you must do it.
The concept of our new project is…
GULPING
It's hiking.
HIKING
HIGH INTENSITY AEROBIC/MUSCULAR EXERCISE
THAT USES THE WHOLE BODY
70% OF SOUTH KOREA IS MOUNTAINOUS
32 MILLION PEOPLE ENJOY HIKING
A LONG-STANDING, TRADITIONAL SPORT
THE GREAT EFFECTS OF K-HIKING
ARE GOING VIRAL ALL AROUND THE WORLD
IMPROVING STAMINA
ENJOYING THE SCENERY
IMPROVING APPETITE
AND CONS
IT'S EXHAUSTING
So it's hiking.
SILENCE
Why are you so quiet?
Well, I'm just so frustrated.
He talked big in the beginning.
-I mean, since it's Producer Nah,
-Right.
I expected something amazing.
Like, "What? He'll help me reach the top?"
HE TRUSTED HIM
I really trusted him.
-Oh, help us reach the top?
-Then hiking? It frustrated me.
Anyway, I can see the point.
Hiking, because…
HE LOOKS DOWN TOO
Seriously, we thought hard,
and it'll be on Netflix.
A lot of foreigners
go hiking in Korea these days.
When they visit Korea,
they go to Jeju Island to hike Hallasan,
then fly to Seoul right after
and take the bus
to Seoraksan Mountain, and…
-That way--
-Come on.
WHO DOES THAT…
DISTRUST
-You can find Reels about it.
-Yes, Reels.
Right upon arriving, they go hiking,
come to Seoul, and go hiking again?
It's called the 3 Peaks Challenge.
HALLASAN, JIRISAN, SEORAKSAN
Many visitors do that in Korea.
That's how popular it is.
And we have four distinct seasons.
But we'll be filming during the winter.
Will we have to wear
some kind of equipment?
Full details will…
GOODBYE THEN
IT WAS NICE MEETING YOU GUYS
Today was…
Just being among you guys
made me so happy.
Come on, hear us out.
All right.
But when we climb down…
I mean, my legs always give out
when I climb down.
Dowoon, how long was your longest hike?
I went up by car to the middle and…
Which mountain?
I think it was Bukhansan?
What about the rest?
Have any of you gone hiking recently?
Well, I did
when I visited our ancestral graves.
INEXPERIENCED BUT VERY FILIAL
That's a hike to me.
Any mountain you want to hike, Chae-min?
-Wait, earlier…
-He answered he hates hiking.
No, I don't hate it.
OUT OF IT
So all of you
don't have much experience in hiking.
INEXPERIENCED FOUR-MAN CREW
Now, the first mountain we'll hike
is very important, right?
-What is it?
-The first mountain we'll hike is…
THEIR FIRST HIKING DESTINATION
…one of the most famous in Korea.
It's Seoraksan Mountain.
That's the one.
NOT VERY HAPPY
RELUCTANT CLAPPING
Seoraksan…
SEORAKSAN MOUNTAIN
THE HEART OF BAEKDUDAEGAN,
THE BACKBONE OF THE KOREAN PENINSULA
IT BOASTS A 1,708 M PEAK: DAECHEONGBONG
SOUTH KOREA'S THIRD-HIGHEST MOUNTAIN
DEEP MOUNTAIN TERRAIN
RUGGED ROCKY RIDGES
LONG AND STEEP TRAILS
TRACES OF TIME
FOOTPRINTS LEFT BY HIKERS
AND THE CHANGING SEASONS
MAKE THE SCENERY EVER-CHANGING
ROUGH YET BEAUTIFUL
SEORAKSAN
I've never been to Seoraksan before.
Same for me. I've never been there.
Same here.
Well, I have had drinks
right under Seoraksan.
Do they have cable cars there?
-They do.
-Cable cars?
So take the cable cars when we come down?
TRYING TO PULL TRICKS
How about we take them when going up?
-That sounds good.
-Right?
BEING SERIOUS
What's really funny is
Chae-min works out the most here
but hates it the most.
TRANSPARENT
Judging by his facial expressions, he's…
He hates sports without a purpose.
BUSTED
He doesn't know why he has to do it.
He's fit enough to do it,
but he can't see
why he has to do it. Right?
Well, I'm sure it'll be fun
doing it with you guys.
EXCELLENT ACTING
That was the most insincere thing
I heard today.
No.
YES
Yes, he looks down.
Although you don't have to be afraid
of going hiking in Seoraksan,
you shouldn't be too relaxed either.
Hiking is also a proper sport
that requires skill.
If we're to do it,
we should learn and do it properly.
So we brought an expert.
-Sir, come in.
-Hello.
Hello.
-It's nice to meet you.
-Hello.
Could you introduce yourself?
I'm an instructor at Korean Alpine School.
I'm Park Min-gu.
CLIMBED SEORAKSAN MORE THAN 300 TIMES
CHAPTER 1
WHAT IS HIKING?
When we hike a mountain,
we usually spend roughly 40%
of our energy going up,
30% coming down,
and save the remaining 30% just in case.
ASCENT 40 : DESCENT 30 : RESERVE 30
While hiking, you get hungry, right?
If your energy is low, what do you do?
-You eat.
It's better to eat before you feel hungry.
Your favorite treats,
snacks, and trail food.
Something you can snack on often,
even if it's low in calories.
How about mandu?
That's not good. Why?
It should be easy to carry.
Something you can eat while you're moving.
-Like energy bars.
-Exactly.
Oh, energy bars.
And you can choose what you prefer.
Then it'll produce energy right away.
And you'll spend it while moving, right?
-Yes.
-How about saving?
-Saving?
The layering system.
-Layering?
-Yes.
To put it simply,
wearing several layers of clothing.
How? Well.
You should do it well.
If you do it carelessly,
it won't be very efficient.
So you must do it well.
CHAPTER 2
THE LAYERING SYSTEM
The layering system
consists of three layers.
First,
the Base Layer for wicking sweat away.
It is recommended to wear moisture-wicking
and quick-drying clothes
to prevent a drop in body temperature.
Second,
the Mid-Layer for insulation.
A fleece is recommended,
but you can also add
a lightweight down jacket if needed.
Third,
the Outer Layer,
a waterproof and windproof layer.
On snowy or stormy days,
it must be worn.
We have gone over the layering system
for winter hiking.
I hope you also make sure
you're properly equipped
before hiking in winter.
PREPARE FOR A SAFE WINTER HIKE WITH GEAR
CHAPTER 3
Q&A
Let's say these four go hiking
in Seoraksan.
-Okay.
-And they've never hiked before.
Its name includes "ak,"
which means "wicked."
-That means it's rough.
-Yes. It's snowy
and has deep and rough terrain.
So with your current stamina,
I don't think you'll pull it off.
Oh, really?
-Then, training…
-So,
we think that snowy mountain hiking
requires twice as much stamina
required for normal hiking.
How long does it take?
That depends on the person.
On average.
That depends on the destination.
To the summit.
Depends on where you start.
From your home.
It has dozens of trails.
14 MAIN TRAILS AND MANY OTHERS
From my home to Seoraksan,
it takes two and a half hours.
To Daecheongbong Peak,
if we start from Sogongwon,
about seven hours?
-Seriously?
-Yes.
If you take it slow, eight hours.
To the top.
Who do you think would hike best?
This one here.
-Him?
-Yes.
I suddenly feel pressure.
LOOKS LIKE AN ACE
It'd be great if we pair up like this.
Two of us and three of them.
Then wouldn't we be
the only ones going up?
What if you take the cable car
and pretend you did it?
BUSTED
But there are no cable cars in Seoraksan.
There aren't?
None to the top.
You can take it to come down, then?
No. How could you, when there are
no cars going up to the top?
Oh, right.
SILLY ME
You're right.
And that's not hiking, that's touring.
CABLE CARS ARE FOR ENJOYING THE SCENERY
-Can I ask a question?
-Yes.
What if you come across wild animals?
Just ignore the wild animals.
-Sorry?
-Ignore them.
Ignore them?
So if a wild boar is in front of me,
I should…
IGNORING
What I mean is…
I should do this?
BIGGER STAGE
What if I'm walking
and it's there, then…
PRETENDING NOT TO SEE IT
That's right.
Should I do this?
This is most important.
There are dangerous wild animals,
and there are cute ones.
You can approach the cute ones,
but wild boars…
If I ignore them, they go away?
It's dangerous to follow them.
STILL IN DOUBT
It's better to move away
without showing your back.
-Then they usually just go away?
-Yes.
-Stay indifferent.
I can do that.
HE'S GOOD AT THAT
You should do that.
What kind of dangerous animals
have you come across while hiking?
A snake.
LESS DANGEROUS THAN EXPECTED
It's quite common to run into wild boars.
We've run into a snake before too.
We should ignore snakes too?
Yes, just pretend not to see them.
-And just go around it.
-But it's hard to ignore snakes.
Because if we lock eyes…
-You were born in the Year of the Snake?
-I can't be sure.
-No, the Horse.
-Oh, really?
Anyway…
But why did you think that?
So if you see any wild animals,
-just… Yes.
-Pretend not to see them.
If you don't provoke them,
DON'T FORGET TO IGNORE THEM
-it won't be dangerous.
-Okay.
-We won't know until we're up there.
-Right.
It's better to try it once
than to hear about it a hundred times.
Today, or when you have time,
if you go hiking nearby, it'll be helpful.
Right. I should go.
-Thank you.
HIKING 101 ENDS
WE PREPARED IT RIGHT AWAY
MEMBERSHIP APPLICATION
HIKING CLUB APPLICATION FORM
TO KEEP THEM FROM LEAVING
THEY FILL IT IN WITHOUT COMPLAINING
"Resolution: Give it your all."
You've changed.
Yes.
But my motto is
"Give up if it's too hard."
Have you checked the club rules, everyone?
Like, "Food is provided
if you complete the hike."
I signed before I read it, darn it.
If you give up halfway,
there will be no food.
Why don't you choose the club president?
Right. We'll take recommendations.
I recommend Tarzzan.
-What?
-One for Tarzzan.
-And Dowoon?
-You should go with the flow.
I recommend Tarzzan too.
Okay, Tarzzan.
Then same for me too.
What…
What about you, Tarzzan?
Tarzzan's shining eyes.
-Of course, I…
-His physical fitness.
And while working with ALLDAY PROJECT,
his mindset has become more suited
to group activities.
There's something you should know.
The president can appoint the manager.
-Hey…
-The manager is lower, right?
Of course.
I like it!
President Tar.
-Manager Car?
-Manager Car.
It's him?
Let's seal it with a round of applause.
But you know what?
The manager manages money.
If we collect a membership fee,
when we eat, you'll…
I might pocket a little.
You should let it slide.
That's embezzlement.
I'll treat you well, so please…
All right.
I'm the president, you know.
PRESIDENT TAR
PRESIDENT TAR WITH ANIMALISTIC ENERGY
Let's go.
We're almost there. Hang in there.
Almost there.
CHEERING THEM UP
What did you write?
"Why are we doing this?"
BUT NOT VERY INTERESTED IN HIKING
WHY ARE WE DOING THIS?
The president started to plan himself.
I did.
EXCELLENT CHOICES OF RESTAURANTS
SATISFIED
-This is so good.
-Good discovery.
Tarzzan found this place?
-Yes, I did.
-It's so good.
Nice discovery.
I might throw up the abalone!
THE PERFECT PLAN EVEN HE'S SATISFIED WITH
I'm sure we'll go
to Ulsan, my hometown, too.
It smells so good.
THEN THEY ARRIVE
AT HIS PARENTS' HOUSE
WHERE A FULL-COURSE MEAL IS SERVED
Let's go!
A MAN-OF-ACTION PRESIDENT
ONLY INTERESTED IN FOOD
I dare you to go.
AND HE IS IN DIFFERENT SPIRITS
It's 32,500 won.
Hey, let's…
Where did they go?
MANAGER CAR
Where are they?
Four bottles of water, please.
PAYING IS ALWAYS HIS JOB
Thank you for the drinks.
I'll pay in cash.
-Thanks.
We have to pay 12,000 won.
All right, I'll pay.
Never thought I'd ride a tandem bike.
PAYING IS EASY
SIGHING
BUT HIKING IS SO HARD
Seriously, this is so crappy.
I hate it.
The mountain's so annoying.
I want to throw away these sticks.
HE SAYS SOMETHING MEAN EVERY TIME HE HIKES
For every negative comment, 100,000 won.
Raise the fine.
-Make it 300,000 won.
-Good.
HE WAS CONFIDENT
I don't think
I can do this program, seriously.
-Wow.
-The fine.
I'm sick of this.
I'm fed up with it.
-Hey.
-Why go up just to come down?
Thanks for the fine.
HE'S ABOUT TO GO BROKE
I'll pay 300,000 won.
THANKS TO HIM,
THEY HAVE MORE THAN ENOUGH MONEY
You know Producer Nah, right?
Please report him to the police.
HIS FINES ARE FEEDING THE MEMBERS
Now…
What are our positions?
For Dowoon, how about
the Minister of Transport?
MINISTER OF TRANSPORT
Here we go.
HE'S SATISFIED WITH HIS POSITION
Let me know if it gets too hard.
I'll be okay.
I'm not that considerate.
HOWEVER
I'll tell you if I'm tired.
I can just drive and pick them up, right?
-Yes.
-Right?
I'm here!
VOLUNTARILY PICKING THEM UP
Have this if you want.
What do you want?
I'll have the Cocoball Bar.
TAKING CARE OF REFUELING TOO
-Here, wear this.
-Okay.
I earned a lot of brownie points.
You're part of ALLDAY PROJECT now.
Let me know if you need food.
HE SEEMS TO ALWAYS SAY THE RIGHT THINGS
I also have candy.
Hey, do you know the Ulsan Alps?
HE'S OFF COURSE
No, the Yeongnam Alps.
HE OFTEN GETS LOST WHILE TALKING
For a second,
I thought there was carbonara in it.
Wait, what was it?
Kkanari something. Darn it.
OFF COURSE AGAIN
Lee Gwang-gyu is from my school too.
-Kim Gwang-gyu?
-Right. Kim Gwang-gyu.
OFF COURSE AGAIN
HE'S BETTER SUITED FOR DRIVING, AFTER ALL
I'm exhausted.
AND THE LAST MEMBER
As the Minister of Foreign Affairs,
my job is
to prevent any conflict between the staff
and the members,
amicably.
His eyes look so beautiful.
-Seriously.
-As if they were photoshopped.
It's not hard.
TAKING THE LEAD
HE CAN EVEN SPEED UP
Should we run for a bit?
To be honest,
I haven't been out of breath at all today.
HE HAS GREAT STAMINA
There's a place for food waste?
This ridge is longer than others?
Isn't the wind speed about 3 m/s tomorrow?
If we bring bottled water tomorrow,
won't it freeze?
What do we do on the last day?
So what's the mission?
What happens if we fail?
But…
The Minister of Foreign Affairs keeps…
ASKING THE STAFF COUNTLESS QUESTIONS
UNTIL HE'S OUT OF BREATH
Since when did your eyes look so defiant?
HIS TRUE COLORS
BEHIND THE GOOD-NATURED FACE
Wrong!
Hey, you…
-No.
-You… What's wrong with you?
-Now…
-They're there.
THE YOUNGER MEMBER
What are you talking about?
AND OLDER MEMBERS ARE NO EXCEPTION
What is it?
GLARING
Chae-min's eyes looked so scary just now.
THE TYRANNICAL MINISTER OF FOREIGN AFFAIRS
He's a tyrant.
FULL OF LAUGHTER WHEN THEY ARE NOT HIKING
HERE COMES A STRANGE HIKING CLUB
"Let's go!" Like this?
-One, two, three.
-Let's go!
THE FUTURE OF INVOLUNTARY BEGINNER HIKERS
JANGGUNBONG
YEONGCHUKSAN
Try your best to look close.
Okay, let's go.
We can't see Baengnokdam from here.
You don't want to see it?
THEY ONLY THINK ABOUT GOING DOWN
-Let's go.
-Let's go!
THEY'RE HAPPY IF THEY DON'T HIKE
Why does one go hiking?
I still don't know.
WILL THEY BE ABLE TO FIND
THE PURPOSE OF HIKING?
HIKING IN SEORAKSAN
BURAMSAN MOUNTAIN, SEOUL
SOMEONE HAS ARRIVED AT BURAMSAN
Hello.
CHAE-MIN CAME TO TRAIN VOLUNTARILY
AS THE INSTRUCTOR ADVISED
FULL HIKING GEAR
-It looks good.
-It does?
-I have a question.
-Okay.
Should I use the sticks from the start?
I think you should, as practice.
Okay, I got it.
Keep it short when going up,
make it long when coming down.
-Right.
-You did your homework.
THE MODEL STUDENT WHO CAME FULLY PREPARED
Rest step?
There's something like that too.
I watched some videos
on YouTube yesterday.
TRAINING IN BURAMSAN BEGINS
It's been so long
since I last went hiking.
The mountain we'll be hiking
is about 1,700 m.
SEORAKSAN ELEVATION: 1,708 M
It's about five times
as long as today's course.
PREPPING FOR SEORAKSAN
I won't have to
work out my legs for a while.
Hiking will do.
Your strides are so long, Chae-min.
STRIDES OF A 190-CM MAN
So you're so fast.
FROM WOODEN STEPS
TO STONE-RIDDLED PATHS, HE HAS NO PROBLEM
INSTRUCTOR'S ADVICE 1
THE LAYERING SYSTEM
INSTRUCTOR'S ADVICE 2
DRINKING WATER OFTEN
INSTRUCTOR'S ADVICE 3
EATING SNACKS TO YOUR LIKING
The candy tastes sweeter today.
CLIMBING STEEP SLOPES AS HE STUDIED
Wow, it's steep.
This is the steepest part.
THE LAST HURDLE TO REACH THE TOP
LOOKING HANDSOME EVEN WITH THE SLOPE
-Is this the top?
-It is.
-How many minutes?
-Fifty-five minutes.
Less than an hour?
Didn't you say it'd take two hours?
LEE CHAE-MIN'S TRAINING IN BURAMSAN
COMPLETED
ACHASAN, SEOUL
Are the trails similar in Seoraksan?
In the beginning, for about an hour.
What about after that?
Will I have to find out there?
At some point, you'll be on all fours.
Like this.
FIRST, PRACTICE WALKING ON TWO LEGS
Slowly. At your own pace.
LONG STRIDES
STAFF
UNEXPECTED
HE'S GOING AHEAD OF THE STAFF
TWO STEPS AT A TIME
Why do my hips hurt?
It proves my poor stamina.
You've only walked for five minutes.
Gosh, I get the feeling.
IT'S NOT EVEN EASY TO WALK ON TWO LEGS
You have long strides since you're tall.
HE WALKS FAST, BUT HE'S ALREADY TIRED
SITS DOWN EVERY CHANCE HE GETS
STILL, HE KEEPS ON WALKING
UNBELIEVABLE…
NOTICEABLY SLOWER ON STEPS
You can see downtown a bit.
But you know what?
I'm not interested in natural scenery.
When we hike Seoraksan,
watch my face closely.
HE KEEPS HIS WORD
TRUDGING
HE DOESN'T CARE ABOUT THE SCENERY
AND WON'T TURN AROUND
It's so tough.
-Five kilometers from now on.
-Okay.
DOWOON RUNNING, TARZZAN WORKING OUT
WITH THE WORLD TOUR AROUND THE CORNER,
HE'S RUNNING AT HANGANG RIVER
WORKING ABROAD,
TARZZAN IS EXERCISING AT THE GYM
Why do we go hiking?
EVERYONE HAS COMPLETED THEIR TRAINING
SAN 27, SEORAK-DONG,
SOKCHO CITY, GANGWON-DO
SEORAKSAN SOGONGWON PARK
SEORAK REST AREA
CURRENT TEMPERATURE
Hello.
TARZZAN ARRIVES
-He's sagging his pants.
-His pants.
My butt's going to freeze.
What's under your nose?
This?
It's an acne patch.
THE PRESIDENT SPRUCED HIMSELF UP
TILTED
I can't give up my style.
THE HIKING BAG HE'S PACKED
FOR THE FIRST TIME
The essentials.
Good morning.
THEY'LL WAIT HERE UNTIL THEY DEPART
Hello.
-They'll be here soon.
-Yes.
FREEZING WEATHER
Seriously, it's so cold.
-Hello.
CHAE-MIN ARRIVES
-Let's mic up first.
How are you feeling?
GRINNING
It's been so long since I went to bed
early. I couldn't sleep.
-Maybe I was nervous, or excited.
-Really?
That's not good.
Hello.
-Hello.
LOOKING UP THE WEATHER FORECAST
What is it?
DOWOON ARRIVES
Is it the sound of the wind? Geez.
It's insane.
It feels a lot colder today.
Right. Why did you pick such a bad day?
HE'S NOT ON HIS WAY TO AN INTERNET CAFE
Geez.
PADDED HAT, PADDED JACKET, PADDED MUFFLER
THEY'RE STILL LOOKING UP THE FORECAST
INTERNET CAFE FASHION
Hello.
Hey.
SYMPATHIZING
Are you all right?
Me? I'm good.
It's -13.8°C, but it feels like -27.5°C.
Minus 27.5°C? That's insane.
Today?
So why did you pick today?
Whose idea was this?
I've never seen -27.5°C before in my life.
It's -27.5°C?
-Yes, -27.5°C.
-Right now?
No one would even go fishing today.
"Feels like"?
But -13.8°C is…
Jung-won isn't here yet?
CHA JUNG-WON, AKA CAR, THE GARDEN, ARRIVES
HE LOOKS JUST LIKE A MOUNTAINEER
HURRYING AS IF BEING CHASED
Hold on. What about meat?
We picked up meat.
Hello.
Hey.
You look like a natural mountaineer.
Gosh, I hate this.
BEING TEASED RIGHT AWAY
God, it's so cold.
Hey, how was it? I heard you went hiking.
-Achasan was not bad.
-Okay.
But they say it's nothing
compared to here.
Really?
Hey, your eyes look so…
unenthusiastic.
What? Don't you remember
what you texted me last night?
"I'm so worried."
COWARD
And you, you went to church yesterday.
Yes, I prayed
that I would come back down safely.
We looked up
today's weather forecast earlier.
The wind chill is about -27°C.
-I've never heard it before.
-Right.
And the real temperature outside is -13°C.
This is so frustrating.
I talked to ChatGPT yesterday.
And it knows I'm Car, the garden.
And I…
It's Huiungak Shelter that's here, right?
I asked if I'd be okay going there,
saying it was my first time.
It said, "No matter
how hot Producer Nah is
and how helpful you think it'll be,
I think you should cancel it."
-Come on.
-I said, "Really?"
"Will I have to pay a penalty fee?"
It said, "Should I look it up for you?"
ChatGPT tried to dissuade me twice.
-Really?
-Yes.
TODAY'S TRAIL
The trail we'll take is
Cheonbuldonggyegok Valley Trail
that ends at Huiungak Shelter.
CHEONBULDONGGYEGOK VALLEY TRAIL
SEORAKSAN'S VALLEYS AND RUGGED PRECIPICE
MAKE BEAUTIFUL SCENERY
IT'S ONE OF THE MAIN TRAILS
KNOWN FOR BEAUTIFUL AUTUMN FOLIAGE
FINAL DESTINATION: HUIUNGAK SHELTER
It is going to take
a little less than five hours going up.
And about ten hours round-trip.
And it's about 17 km.
SEORAKSAN SOGONGWON FRONT GATE
GWIMYEONAM ROCK
HUIUNGAK SHELTER
For the first hour, the walk will be easy.
In the middle, it'll get a bit tougher.
And for the last two hours,
a very challenging trail awaits you.
IT'LL BE A HARD JOURNEY
FOR THE BEGINNER HIKERS
So that's our plan.
And since today's our first filming,
let me briefly explain
the system of our show, Take a Hike!
We're going to conquer the most symbolic
and beautiful mountains in Korea
one by one.
We wanted to test you
to see if you're ready for the quest.
So we picked this mountain
that's not included in the quest.
-What?
Today,
just consider it
as pre-season training.
I mean, we're not even going
for the summit.
Just the shelter.
We'll just touch the shelter
and come down.
So after seeing how well you hike today,
we'll decide
how we'll give you the next one and when.
We can't let just anyone do it.
They might get hurt
or get into an accident.
I'm that "just anyone."
I'm no one special. I'm nothing.
Seriously, I…
JUST ANYONE
What's important is
that we shouldn't do too well today.
"Shouldn't"?
Let's collapse halfway.
Then some of us
might get eliminated today?
If you do badly.
Is it a survival show?
This, plus survival? That's absurd.
You might be able to drop out.
INTRIGUED
That's what you want.
HIS WISH: DROPPING OUT
5 MINUTES BEFORE DEPARTURE
I never thought
I'd do a show about hiking.
And why did it have to be with us?
You thought the same, right?
Be honest.
I almost said it out loud but held it.
Because it's pointless now.
It's too late?
NO BACKSIES
HIKING BEGINS
Look, the sun's rising.
It feels nice.
I suddenly feel so good.
It's been a while
since I was awake at this hour.
I'll take a photo now. I'll be quick.
You can look here.
TAKING PICTURES IS A MUST WHEN HIKING
Look at the camera.
THEY DON'T WANT TO DO IT
One more time.
Say "let's go!"
"Let's go!" Like this.
Now, one, two, three.
-Let's go!
-One, two, three.
AT SEORAKSAN SOGONGWON PARK
ON JAN 12, 2026
What is this?
THEY FIND IT RIDICULOUS
It's not as cold as I expected.
CONDUCTED UNDER THE SUPERVISION
OF PROFESSIONALS
-Compared to before…
-Is it better?
SEORAKSAN SOGONGWON FRONT GATE
I didn't know
the sticks would feel so awkward.
You must think they're your own legs.
Hey, the screen's not even on yet.
Exactly. My goodness.
Then maybe we're the first hikers today.
The paths will be like this until the end?
No. Never.
-"Never."
-I've only been to Namsan.
That'd be so nice.
THE INEXPERIENCED PRESIDENT
Wow, that must be it.
It is beautiful.
It's still snowy.
It's so beautiful.
I really enjoyed it.
Ending now would be perfect.
You know, if you grill meat here,
it tastes even better.
LUNCH: PORK BELLY
Seriously.
Wow, it's so pretty over there.
I think the cable cars
must be around here.
Yes, Kwon Geumseong on your left
is where the cable car goes up.
HERE
SEORAKSAN CABLE CAR
YOU CAN GO UP
TO KWON GEUMSEONG COMFORTABLY
AND ENJOY THE MAGNIFICENT SCENERY
KWON GEUMSEONG FORTRESS
NOJEOKBONG PEAK & TOWANGSEONGPOKPO FALLS
STRONG WIND
It's so cold.
-So cold.
Wow, my face feels so cold.
-Me too.
-I should cover it.
PUTTING ON THE BALACLAVA
Maybe I should've brought that too.
Now that I've covered my face,
it's much better.
THE TWO WHO BROUGHT BALACLAVAS
I should've brought one.
THE TWO WHO DIDN'T
It's definitely better.
-Definitely better.
-Definitely.
You're still not true celebs.
You shouldn't cover your faces.
Cameras are rolling.
Thank you!
6TH YEAR, 2ND YEAR, 12TH YEAR, 14TH YEAR
But I think it's okay
for me to cover mine.
This is Sinheungsa Temple.
You're going through Sinheungsa.
There's a big statue
of the Buddha on your right.
Wow, it's huge.
SINHEUNGSA TEMPLE
A HISTORIC TEMPLE SITUATED
ON THE SLOPES OF SEORAKSAN
KNOWN FOR ITS PEACEFUL AMBIENCE
AND BIG BRONZE STATUE OF THE BUDDHA
Well, I'm a Christian.
But I'm sure they're close.
God and the Buddha? Of course.
We'll be back safely.
Please wish us luck.
PRAYING
What you see on your right
is Ulsanbawi Rock.
My hometown, Ulsan.
ULSANBAWI ROCK
ONE OF THE MOST SYMBOLIC ATTRACTIONS
OF SEORAKSAN
THE HUGE SAWTOOTH-LIKE ROCKY PEAKS
PRESENT A GRAND SITE
On your left, a lot of snow has piled up
on the summit.
Is that Daecheongbong Peak?
It is.
-That one?
-Yes.
-Are we going there?
-No, not there.
On your left. We're not going there,
but our destination is on the way there.
DAECHEONGBONG PEAK
THE HIGHEST AND MOST SYMBOLIC PEAK
IN SEORAKSAN
YOU CAN ENJOY THE SCENERY
OF THE MAGNIFICENT TERRAIN
AND THE VIEW STRETCHING TO THE EAST SEA
DAECHEONGBONG
My problem is,
I'm not interested
-in natural scenery.
-Seriously?
So when I went hiking in Seoul,
the staff were like,
"You can see downtown Seoul from here."
But I was just not interested at all.
I just don't care about it.
I used to fight with my ex-girlfriends
a lot because of it.
"Then why did we come here?"
"Because you wanted to."
And the question
I'm least interested in is
"Do you like mountains or the sea?"
Only the accommodation matters to me.
Surely, snowy mountains will be different.
I bet they are.
SINHEUNGSA TEMPLE
DIFFICULTY: EASY
You'll walk like this
for another 30 minutes.
The air is so fresh.
It's nice.
That's a perfect uphill trail.
Right.
Like this,
I can keep going.
-Seriously, even for ten hours.
-Yes.
HOWEVER
All right, the paved trail ends here.
-Okay.
PROPER HIKING TRAILS BEGIN HERE
STRIDING
We must be quick walkers indeed.
Right. You're just
walking normally, right?
Yes.
I bet you normally walk faster.
Yes. I'm trying my best to keep pace.
Oh, really?
-Let's keep pace with Tarzzan.
-Okay.
TARZZAN
It's just the beginning.
-You're feeling it, right?
-Yes.
I feel it right away. So annoying.
I think it'll be hard to talk later.
It's so cold.
-My lips already feel stiff.
-Me too.
My mouth is freezing, and it's exhausting.
Let's talk a lot when we come down.
I think we can save chatting
for when we're back down.
I'll explain it briefly.
These rocks here.
They're called "Kissing Rocks."
Oh, right.
All right, let's move on.
Don't make us stop
for something like that.
"Kissing Rocks"?
I mean, don't we
look like trainees in boot camp?
Right.
WEEK 4 TRAINING MARCH
-They're different ages, right?
-Exactly.
This is called "Waseondae."
"Waseondae"?
Yes, Waseondae,
because it's said that a hermit
once lay here admiring the scenery.
So where did the hermit lie?
-Where?
-I think it's the rock over there.
If we go up further, there's a wide rock.
Just a bit further.
I think this rock is Waseondae.
You think, or you're sure?
I'm sure.
BAD DOCENT
They all look the same.
Very well.
MEANWHILE
THE STATUS OF PRESIDENT TAR'S PANTS
THE WORLD'S FIRST HIKER WITH SAGGING PANTS
I bet his butt's freezing.
Right.
-Tarzzan.
-Yes?
Your butt's not cold?
No, the pants inside are warmer.
The ones outside are thin.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
The pants are too big for me.
I see.
-That's so cute.
-It's very hip hop.
What you see on your right
is Biseondae Rock. We'll head toward it.
THE EASY PART IS OVER
The wind's getting colder.
Without trees, it's so windy.
Gosh, my face is freezing.
CURRENT WIND DIRECTION: WEST
SPEED: 15.9 M/S
THE VALLEY'S FROZEN DUE TO A COLD WAVE
WITH WIND GETTING STRONGER
IT FEELS BLEAK
When I walked through the valley,
I felt a bit afraid.
And I also felt overwhelmed
by Mother Nature.
Wow, it's frozen hard.
It's all frozen.
CONTINUOUS STEPS ALONG THE VALLEY
Damn steps.
What did you think of your pace?
-It was good in the beginning.
-It was?
-I thought I could get through it.
-However…
Then it got harder and harder.
Yes.
One, two, three.
THIS IS THE PRELUDE TO GREAT SUFFERING
1 HOUR INTO HIKING
THEY ARRIVE AT BISEONDAE ROCK
This is an easy course?
No, it's moderate.
DIFFICULTY: MODERATE
FLAT TRAIL
METAL STEPS
ROCKY STEPS
THE EVER-CHANGING PATH OF A MODERATE TRAIL
LEAD: CAR, THE GARDEN
MIDDLE 1: DOWOON
MIDDLE 2: TARZZAN
TAIL: CHAE-MIN
1ST LINEUP OF SEORAKSAN HIKING
Is the pace good?
-I can just keep going, right?
-Yes.
It's good.
It's not that fast.
You can go faster if you want.
Don't worry about us.
But I'm tired.
Already.
LOW STAMINA, FAST WALKER
BUT HE GOES SLOW ON STEPS
"A HIGHLY SKILLED MOUNTAINEER
TAKES HIS TIME
AND ALWAYS CLIMBS AT HIS OWN PACE."
-FRANK SMYTHE
Damn it.
STEPS YET AGAIN
"ALPINISM IS THE ART OF SUFFERING."
-VOYTEK KURTYKA
"OVER EVERY MOUNTAIN, THERE IS A PATH,
ALTHOUGH IT MAY NOT BE SEEN
FROM THE VALLEY." -THEODORE ROETHKE
Watch for snow.
AN ICY SECTION BEGINS
Wow, there's snow now.
SLIPPERY
SLIP
We'll put on crampons after this part.
They say it's getting icier.
Be careful of this rock.
-Be careful here.
-Okay.
1 HOUR AND 15 MINUTES INTO HIKING
THEY PUT ON CRAMPONS
WHAT ARE CRAMPONS?
TRACTION DEVICES
CONSISTING OF METAL SPIKES
PUT ON OVER HIKING BOOTS
TO PREVENT SLIPPING
-Like this?
-Yes.
-This is correct?
-Is this right?
-Yes, all the way.
The grip sure is much better.
CHAE-MIN PRACTICED IT IN BURAMSAN
THE PROPER WAY TO PUT ON CRAMPONS
All done.
MEANWHILE, IT'S THE FIRST TIME
FOR PRESIDENT TAR
GIVING IT A TRY WITH PASSION
It sure feels different.
You did well.
Of course. I practiced.
-You did?
-Yes.
I can't see my face.
CHECKING HIS APPEARANCE BRIEFLY
Does it feel like hiking now?
Well, it's fun.
It's tough. It's been a while.
How are you feeling, guys? Are you okay?
It's tough.
Everyone's talking less.
You look okay. Is it doable?
It's not bad. Better than I thought.
THEY SET OUT AGAIN
-You okay?
-Yes.
It sure is different.
It was so slippery earlier.
Right.
Wow, it's good.
A DOWNHILL PART RIGHT AWAY
It's not slippery now.
AMAZED
The grip's insane.
It feels like I'm wearing
those spike shoes.
Doesn't it feel so soft?
Yes, it feels so nice.
It feels so soft on the ground.
I realized that they were essentials
when there was snow.
Honestly, when I packed my bag,
I thought, "I'm not climbing
the Himalayas. I wouldn't be using them."
But wow, they were lifesavers for me.
-This sure is different.
-It's so good.
I'm more stable now.
I feel like
my stamina's being recharged.
New items acquired.
I realized they were a must.
They say the right equipment
can be very helpful.
That's especially true in snowy mountains.
I'm getting hungry.
-Right?
-I'm feeling hungry.
I'm hungry.
-Are we halfway there now?
-Halfway?
Not halfway yet.
SIGHS
MEANWHILE, CHAE-MIN'S POINT OF VIEW
SAGGING
I watched his butt
the whole time I was climbing.
And he didn't give it up.
But that's commendable.
I wanted to look better and cooler too,
but I didn't have the energy.
It was just so tough as it was.
But he…
He still had the energy to pull it up.
ONCE
TWICE
927TH TIME
20,020,927TH TIME
The pants…
I didn't mean to sag them.
I was going to wear
just one layer of pants,
but it felt so cold.
So I wore another pair of sweatpants
and then the pants.
But the problem was,
it was hard to know
the pants were slipping down,
and Chae-min kept telling me
they were slipping down,
so I kept pulling them up.
I was never doing it intentionally
to try to look cool.
Never. Please don't misunderstand.
Wow, it's getting snowy now.
THE HIGHER THEY GET, THE SNOWIER IT GETS
Water's still flowing.
I'm too busy watching the ground
to enjoy the scenery.
Exactly.
The sound of snow is so nice.
-What?
-The sound of snow.
-It's nice.
-Right.
With the crampons on…
It's even better.
It's endless steps from now on.
Oh, dear.
ENDLESS ROCKY STEPS
THE STAFF'S PICK
1ST CRUX
CAR, THE GARDEN IS STILL IN THE LEAD
"THE MOMENT YOU OVERCOME YOURSELF,
YOU'RE AT THE TOP." -HEO YOUNG-HO
Geez.
It's killing me.
"THE STEEPER THE PATH,
THE HARDER MY HEART BEATS." -NIETZSCHE
SIGHS
GRUNTS
"IF THE SUBJECT LOOKS SMALLER,
THEY'VE FALLEN BEHIND." -HONG DEOK-HWAN
DIRECTOR HONG DEOK-HWAN
SIGHS
Let's go.
God, I'm exhausted.
STEPS BLOCK HIS WAY
SIGHS
Go ahead.
THE LEAD CHANGED
GRINNING
-We'll take a break at Gwimyeonam Rock.
-Okay.
STAGGERING
It's too tough.
Sit down here.
How about we sit down on the bench?
Careful.
Are you okay?
I'm okay. I'm fine.
Come and sit here.
CHECKING THE MAP MEANINGLESSLY
1 HOUR AND 55 MINUTES INTO HIKING
1ST BREAK
We can still see it.
This is
called Gwimyeonam Rock.
It was your first crux.
So, it's about a third of the way.
-Good.
-Drink some water.
And if you want to eat your food,
you can have it here before we move.
Where was the toughest?
Just now.
Remember your first crux?
When you got there, how did you feel?
At that point,
I started having the same thoughts
I'd had from the beginning.
"Why did I decide to do this?"
I usually never do something
that I know I can't do.
I mean, the moment you said it was hiking,
I should've walked away.
I mean it. Seriously.
It's like a slushie now.
Stop filming me!
WARNING
SLIPPERY
What? Your hat!
It blew away?
Some of the memories are gone, seriously.
I really hoped he'd drop out.
I was like,
"If he drops out, I'll do it too. Yay!"
Subtitle translation by: Wayne Ryu